The city lights are fading in the glass Watching
the broken billboards flying past Ten years of
playing at a scripted scene Caught in the teeth
of the machine I drop the window, let the cold air
in Shedding the ghost of who I've always been
There's a million voices trying to pull me back
But the tires are humming on the open track Yeah,
the tires are humming on the open track And it's
just static On the dial, turning the knob for
another mile Fading out the echoes of the things
they said Cutting the wire inside my head Out
here on the highway, running wild Leaving the
static on the dial
They try to tell us what the frequency should be,
selling a plastic kind of fantasy. But out in the
desert where the signal dies, you finally see
the open skies. Heaven is holding down the
rhythm line. Tyler is keeping us right on time
There's a million voices trying to pull me back
But the tires are humming on the open track Yeah,
the tires are humming on the open track And it's
just static on the dial Turning the knob for
another mile Fading out the echoes of the things
they said Cutting the wire inside my head Out
here on the highway, running wild Leaving the
static on the dial
Tune it out, let the frequency fade
Tune it out, leave the mess that they made
Cause it's just static on the dial Turning the
knob for another mile Fading out the echoes of
the things they said Cutting the wire inside my
head Out here on the highway, running wild
Leaving the static on the dial Just static
fading away
Nothing but the open road today